Lynchburg Va, 24502 (540) 524-0245

charlestbell@gmail.com

GitHub - https://github.com/charlestbell

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/c-t-bell-9b03bb63/

C.T. Bell

SUMMARY:

Full Stack web developer with a certificate from the UCR Bootcamp. 5 years of ecommerce experience and 10 years of video marketing experience, Fluent in Node, Mongo, Express, React, HTML5, CSS and SQL. A life-long learner with a passion for user experience and design. Excellent communicator. Highly creative and able to understand complex systems. Experience with Agile Development and kanban. Known for being adaptable, learning new things quickly and over-delivering.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

CODING: Node, Mongo, Express, React, SQL HTML5 and CSS

TOOLS: GIT, Heroku, Photoshop

PROJECTS:

 Dablr A social education platform that aggregates the best tutorials on every topic. | Sequelize, SQL, JQuery, Bootstrap

> Live Site - https://dabblr-tutorials.herokuapp.com/ Repo - https://github.com/Relten98/Dabblr

 ctyFaktz A data-driven dashboard that generates interesting facts about any city on the fly | Materialize, jQuery

Live Site - https://charlestbell.github.io/ctyFaktz/

Repo - https://github.com/charlestbell/ctyFaktz

Weather Dashboard A beautiful and personal weather dashboard | Bootstrap,
jQuery

Live Site - https://charlestbell.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

Repo - https://github.com/charlestbell/Weather-Dashboard

Day Scheduler A browser-based hourly day planner | Bootstrap, jQuery

Live Site - https://charlestbell.github.io/Day-Scheduler/

Repo - https://github.com/charlestbell/Day-Scheduler

EXPERIENCE:

Web Admin/Marketer/Content Creator - Employee Blue Ridge Overland Gear

2016-2021 Lynchburg, VA

March 2016 - Present

- Planned, produced and edited over 300 Youtube across multiple brands, one in particular went from 1k subscribers to well over 20k
- Helped to craft the brand identity, developing messaging, strategies and marketing materials and helped take the company from 6 employees to 16 and triple it's sales.
- Helped facilitate a successful website replatforming. Worked on database transfer, content audit and implementation for various brand needs. Quickly became the go-to person for technical needs.

Freelance Film Crew

2010 - 2016 Virginia area

 Worked on content and marketing for countless brands and several award winning film projects.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate UCR

Nov 2020 - April 2021

AWARDS

CyberPatriot Team Lead - 2nd in Virginia 2011